QQ飞车

http://speed.qq.com

QQ Speed is the most interesting and the most fashionable online racing casual game which Tencent has independently developed. It is completely free, and players can directly log in with their QQ accounts. QQ Speed uses the internationally advanced physical engine PhysX to create a true sense of a car racer. Its unique "Border War", romantic "Inter-City Friend Making", fashionable 3D roles, brilliant racing course scenes and a true sense of drifting will bring you to an inspirational top speed world! On January 23, 2009, QQ Speed passes its first anniversary of open beta. Currently, the game has over 100 million registered users and more than 450,000 concurrent online users. QQ Speed is truly the most mainstream online racing game in China.


零度游戏源码整理提供